[LUNA]
Adventurer Kazuma Satou.
May I present to you
your grand bounty
for defeating the Devil King's
General Sylvia.
Three hundred million eris!
[cheering]
At this point you're
the guild's ace in the hole!
[SAKAMAKI] He did great work
at the capital, too!
[ADVENTURER 07-A (F)]
Hard to believe toads used
to give him trouble!
- Nice job!
- Thanks!
I knew you were gonna do
something great
all along, Kazuma!
[ADVENTURER 07-B (M)] And as
a member of the weakest class,
no less!
Now, now, flattery's not gonna
get you anything, folks.
[KAZUMA]
Except...
A round of the best bubbly
this joint has to offer!
- Ha-ha, yeah!
- [cheering]
- Drink up, everybody!
- [cheering] -[laughs]
[ADVENTURER 07-C (F)]
Kazuma, will you marry me?
[KAZUMA] Sure! -[ADVENTURER]
Be my sugar daddy!
[KAZUMA]
You got it!
[hands clapping]
[KAZUMA] Who's
responsible for this meal?
Inform the chef
that Kazuma Satou,
the famous collector
of multiple bounties,
requires his presence
immediately!
[AQUA] As does the incomparably
beautiful arch priest Aqua!
[gulps]
[CHEF 07-A (M)] Um,
is there some sort of problem
with your meal, sir?
No, I merely wish to offer
my compliments for the cuisine.
Even castle finery can't leave
such a remarkable impression,
I must say.
[CHEF 07-A (M)]
Oh, thank you very much!
♪
[sighs]
Now don't tell me, the stew's
secret ingredient is wine.
Ah.
♪
[AQUA]
It's tart, so I'd guess a red.
The vintage...
a 30-year old Romanee Conti.
Hmm.
How did I do?
[CHEF 07-A (M)]
It's the cheap stuff.
Oh.
[AQUA] Well, it's impressive
you've managed to get
this much flavor
from inexpensive liquor.
You're far too kind,
thank you so much.
I did enjoy the stew,
but the fish
had my tongue in ecstasy.
[KAZUMA] If I were
to describe the flavor.
[chewing]
It's like sneaking
into your girlfriend's room,
opening up her closet
with excitement
only to find a mimic inside!
It just had such
an explosive impact on me.
♪
You get me, don't you, chef?
[CHEF 07-A (M)]
I do not, sir.
Okay.
[KAZUMA]
Well, it's super good!
Adventurer Kazuma Satou gives
this establishment three stars!
[AQUA]
And another three from me, too.
Thank you both very much.
I shall endeavor to earn
four stars from you
the next time you visit.
[scoffs]
How very bold of you!
[KAZUMA]
And, for a job well done...
[coins clanking]
...you can keep
the change as a tip.
[AQUA]
Yes, thank you for the meal.
[CHEF 07-A (M)] You've paid
exact change, actually.
But that's okay, we'd love
to have you back, any time!
[Aqua humming]
I like that chef,
he's a good guy!
I think maybe I'd like
to go back tomorrow
and order
the place's best bubbly.
- Now, now.
- Huh?
We already have reservations
at the place
with the secret menu
tomorrow, remember?
Oops, I forgot.
[both laughing]
♪
We're home.
[gasping]
[MEGUMIN] Here you go,
that's what you want, isn't it?
You're a perverted
little Crusader, huh?
I'm not giving in
no matter what you do!
[both whimpering]
No, it's not
what it looks like!
Please, come back!
Don't get the wrong idea!
Hey, it's all good, Aqua and I
can just go grab another meal,
you two can have the house
to yourselves tonight!
We certainly wouldn't want to
get in the middle of anything!
The Axis Order recognizes
all manner
of romantic relationships.
So if you two need
blessing magic or anything.
No, that is not
what's happening here!
[MEGUMIN]
Konosuba!
[breathing heavily]
♪
I'm helping Darkness prepare
for the endurance competition.
Wait, what competition?
[MEGUMIN] Turns out Darkness
is the reigning champion
of an endurance contest
that's held every summer.
No, knock it off!
It would have been nice if you
two practiced at her place.
It feels
like a furnace in here.
[DARKNESS] My father hasn't
been feeling very well lately.
I wouldn't want to give him
any reason to worry about me.
And he might get worse
if he found out
what his only daughter
was doing with her time.
What do you mean?
You don't want him
to find out you're a pervert?
[sighs]
My heat resistance
is even better.
Maybe because I've
leveled up since last year.
Oh, Kazuma,
I was wondering if you...
- Kazuma?
- Huh?
Well, well...
what does this remind me of?
What are you talking abo--
[gasping]
You...
You don't mean?
[KAZUMA] If it isn't
the great Crusader Darkness
who had so much fun making
a fool of me at the capital.
[whimpers]
And that Crusader is completely
helpless right now!
[snickers]
Somebody put me
out of my misery,
I'm begging you please,
don't let this happen!
[GROUP]
Konosuba!
[sighs]
Kazuma, you took
advantage of my defenseless,
overheating body.
Whoa, don't say it like that!
I just tickled you
till you passed out.
Oh, Darkness.
Whatever happened
to the proud Crusader
I remember seeing
at the capital?
[KAZUMA]
What is that?
Ah... have I piqued
your curiosity?
Then allow me to enlighten you!
And feast your eyes on this!
Have you ever seen
a real dragon egg?
[GROUP]
Dragon egg?!
[AQUA] The other day,
I had the house to myself.
♪
An honor and a privilege
to meet you, my dear!
And you are?
I have spent a great
deal of time
seeking out adventurers
such as yourself
who are capable of tangling
with the Devil King's forces!
And what a treat this is!
I didn't expect you
to be so beautiful!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I suppose it's true
you won't find many
who can compare to me.
Hmm.
And for bravely facing down
the forces of evil
with no thought for your
own safety, I present...
[AQUA]
What is it?
[SALESMAN 07-A (M)]
This is a genuine dragon egg!
- [AQUA] Dragon?
- [SALESMAN 07-A (M)] Indeed!
[SALESMAN 07-A (M)] A treasure
like this cannot be acquired
through mere wealth, of course.
But I wish to give it to you
for your upcoming
confrontation with
the Devil King.
Really?
I would think it would cost
hundreds of millions
to get your hands on
something like a dragon egg.
No, no, no, no, my dear,
I insist!
I have traveled long and far
to leave this egg
in your incredibly
capable hands!
- Although...
- What is it?
No one's watching,
no one's listening.
I had some expenses
getting it here...
♪
Oh, no.
How much did you pay him?
It was a steal!
He said I could take it for
whatever cash I had on hand.
Why aren't all guys that nice?
Ohh!
[AQUA] I've already picked out
a name: Zeltman Kingsford.
And since I'm raising him,
you know some day,
he'll be the emperor
of all dragons.
They'll call him Emperor Zel.
[KAZUMA]
You moron!
♪
[LITTLE GIRL 07-A (F)]
Morning!
[AQUA]
This is ridiculous.
What if Emperor Zel needs me?
Let's get this over with.
Worried about your chicken?
[AQUA]
He is not a chicken!
- [KAZUMA] Yeah, he is.
- [AQUA] No, he's a dragon!
- [KAZUMA] He's a chicken.
- He's a dragon
and I gave him a lovely name
and that name is Emperor Zel!
- Okay, fine.
- [growling]
Whatever he is, we've got more
important stuff to deal with.
♪
AQUA]
Hey, open up!
You don't want to keep
your most important
business partner waiting,
do you?
Open up this door right now!
Have you any idea
what time it is?
You're always busy
in the afternoon
so we figured
we'd do you a favor
and come here first thing
in the morning,
no need to thank us.
You are a terrible nuisance
to your neighbors, you menace!
[growling]
[VANIR] I take it you're here
about the boy's reward?
Well, get inside, then.
[GROUP]
Konosuba!
[VANIR]
As promised.
[chuckles]
You're welcome!
Because I'm sure
you were gonna say,
"Thank you for taking the time
to meet with
a puny demon like me,"
wasn't it you ingrate?"
Cease your prattle!
Or I shall make your
hindquarters produce aloe vera!
The proprietor of this
establishment is overworked
and trying to rest in the back!
So try to be quiet!
[KAZUMA]
Business has been that good?
Yes.
There's been no shortage
of merriment around here.
[KAZUMA] Nice! -I had
something of an epiphany.
- [KAZUMA] About what?
- I realized
how to prevent our troublesome
and determined
little entrepreneur
from incurring debt
any further.
Thanks so much,
your patronage is appreciated.
[VANIR] You see, it's only
when she has free time
on her hands that
she starts causing problems.
[Wiz screams]
[VANIR] Thus, I've endeavored
to ensure she's occupied
24 hours a day,
even without
a moment for a meal!
Two weeks have passed
without any trouble at all!
[WIZ] Thank you! -[VANIR]
Although she has started crying
and laughing without cause,
among other such outbursts.
[VANIR] Hardly a condition
fit for customer service.
Hence, she rests.
[WIZ]
Your patronage...
- [DULLAHAN]
Join me! Cross over!
- [WIZ] Thank you.
Yeah, I know liches
are supposed to be immortal
but that's still pretty brutal.
- [VANIR] By the way...
- Ugh?
You're the woman tormented
by her flushed body,
who spends all her nights--
[screams]
[KAZUMA]
Hey, finish your sentence!
What does she spend
her nights doing?
Shut up, stop talking, Kazuma!
Such intense negativity
and shame.
What a treat.
- [whimpering]
- [VANIR] Armor girl.
[VANIR] There is a shadow
of destruction around you.
♪
The murky presence
of that nuisance of a woman
is clouding my vision
of the future a bit.
But I feel I owe you.
I should like
to give you a reading.
[sighs]
Hey, when you said "nuisance"
who were you talking about?
Even the dimmest star
in the sky
could figure that one out.
Ah, I'm gonna take
your stupid mask!
[VANIR]
Get your holy mitts off!
Shadow of destruction, huh?
Hey, quit your groping
and tell me
what you were about to say
about Darkness, I need details!
[screams]
[KAZUMA]
I think she crushed a molar.
I'm going to start
by asking you a few questions.
[AQUA]
It's all gonna be okay.
They may make you
uncomfortable,
but please answer them
honestly.
[sighs]
[VANIR]
Let's begin.
First question,
you are a Crusader.
So why have you
been making efforts
to lighten your armor
as of late?
My clumsiness gets in the way.
If my armor was lighter,
I thought it would help
make my attacks more accurate.
Ahh!
Wow, Darkness, you really
thought this through!
I thought I told you
to answer honestly?
[gasps]
I... It's just that my abs
have gotten
really well-defined lately.
♪
So, I...made my armor lighter
to stop gaining muscle.
- [whimpers]
- [KAZUMA] She's shredded now?
Very good,
let's move on to the next one.
[VANIR] A wizard's dress
was left in the laundry basket.
[gasps]
[VANIR] When you left the bath,
why did you take it?
And sneakily
hold it to your body,
muttering, "No.
No, there's no way?"
[DARKNESS]
No. No, there's no way.
[VANIR] And despite
this alleged denial...
[whimpering]
[VANIR] All the while,
you observed yourself
in the mirror,
tilted your head
to the side, and smiled.
Why?
[whimpering]
Cute clothes never look
good on me,
and I can't go shopping
for them, it's embarrassing!
But then I saw it
lying there, and I...
I thought I'd try it
and see how it looked.
[sobbing]
[DARKNESS] I'm sorry a brutish
and muscular woman like me
would dare to even hold
such cute clothing!
I'm so sorry,
please forgive me!
[AQUA] Hey, I bet
you'd look beautiful
in any cute little dress
you can find, Darkness!
I've seen you wear
cute dresses before!
You're not hurting anybody
trying stuff on
in the privacy
of your own bedroom!
Right?
[soft whimper]
One more question for you.
[VANIR] Knowing that
the lecherous boy lusts for you
as he does, why is it that
you choose to wear clothing
that accentuates your figure?
Stop, do I really need
to answer these questions
before you'll tell me
my fortune?
Huh?
[VANIR] When did I say
the questions had anything
to do with the reading
I was going to give you?
Oh, what...
For that you need only put your
hand against the crystal ball.
I was merely making
conversati--
I'm gonna rip you to pieces!
[VANIR]
Please, don't touch the mask!
I was right.
[VANIR] There is a shadow
of destruction around you.
Disaster awaits your
family home, and your father.
[sighs]
♪
Your intelligence is lacking.
So you will attempt
something rash,
like self-sacrifice,
to avert this fate.
But all your efforts
will be in vain.
Oh, yes.
As far as I can see,
you're powerless to stop it.
[grunts]
You'd be wise to abandon
everything and flee.
The lecherous boy
would elope with you, I'm sure.
Strangely, he believes
you to be willing,
but his fear of rejection
keeps him timid.
Hey, take it easy!
You can't just say
stuff like that!
I swear, every time
you open your mouth
you're sabotaging
every meaningful relationship
I've ever had!
- Listen, Vanir.
- [VANIR] Hm?
I appreciate the advice.
Thanks,
I'll try to keep it in mind.
[sighs]
Kazuma,
we've got plenty of money.
[DARKNESS] I assume we won't be
accepting quests for some time?
Nothing I heard here
concerns me very much.
So I'll visit my father
since it's been a while.
[KAZUMA]
Oh, okay.
[chuckles]
[door closes]
- [VANIR] Boy.
- Huh?
[whistling]
[VANIR] I have a small
prophecy for you too.
[VANIR]
No brand is truly successful
selling just one product.
Do not be satisfied
with past victories.
I told the girl
she is powerless.
And it's true, she can do
nothing to avoid her fate.
However, depending
on your level of effort,
the same may
not be true for you.
- [water rippling]
- Ah?
Yes.
[groaning]
[crows cawing]
[KAZUMA]
So much for that.
♪
[cat meowing]
Chomusuke, you don't even
shed in the summertime, huh?
[cat meowing]
- Kazuma!
- [screaming]
Hey, what the hell,
don't you know how to knock?
Let's collect the bounty
on this monster!
You are aware
it's completely uncouth
for an unmarried noblewoman
to be staying out
all night, right?
Shut up,
I wasn't out all night!
And take a look at this.
[KAZUMA]
A Kowloon Hydra?
[DARKNESS]
And it's got a huge bounty!
I think we should claim it.
I believe it was hibernating
at the bottom of a lake,
but it just woke up.
And you want us
to take care of it?
Stop pitching ideas
you come up with
when you're half-asleep.
Axel needs us to defend it,
don't you care?
[gasps]
You are the hero who slayed
the generals of the Devil King.
Kazuma Satou, come on!
This must answer the call!
You think you can butter me up
and get me to put
my life at risk
just by calling me a hero?
We've got plenty
of money as it is.
Gimme a break!
We've known each other
for how long
and that's the best
you come up with?
[whimpering]
Gimme some motivation
if that's what you want!
Surely you can think
of an idea or two!
Gah!
All right, if I must.
Upon our completion
of the quest.
Um, I'll reward you with, uh...
[KAZUMA]
With what?
What are you gonna do for me?
I... I'll kiss you
on the cheek.
[groaning]
- [KAZUMA] Nuh-uh.
- Huh?
Wait, what?
You think I'm gonna
risk my life
for a measly little kiss?
Wha... I thought
that's what you wanted!
[cat meowing]
Ya hear that, Chomusuke?
You believe this lady?
She honestly thinks that
it'd be worth risking your life
just to get one tiny
little kiss from her.
Isn't that the most
self-absorbed thing
you've ever heard?
[whimpering]
You little creep,
I was just trying to be nice!
- Woah!
- [cat meowing]
Violence is not the answer!
Ah?
♪
Kazuma, do you mean it?
You won't do it?
♪
[gasps]
[KAZUMA]
How could I turn you down
with those crocodile tears!
[AQUA]
No!
I don't wanna fight a hydra!
What's Darkness gonna do
with a bounty like that anyway?
Did her family really lose
all of their money?
[screaming]
Hydras are a class of dragon!
Once it's removed,
people will call me
a Dragon Slayer!
I shall finally claim
the title I've always wanted!
Why in the world would you
want a title like that,
we'll have a dragon
in the house
once Emperor Zel is hatched!
[grunting]
And I hate having
to leave him at Wiz's store!
Not a lot of options.
We don't know anybody else
we could sucker in
to helping you hatch
your dumb egg.
I worry about the influence
egg-sitters like a lich
and a demon could have
on such an impressionable mind!
Please!
When a dragon
is still in their egg,
the more time a parent
spends taking care of them,
the more magical power
they'll develop,
and the more my dragon
will take after me!
[AQUA] I want Emperor Zel
to be a sacred white dragon.
[AQUA] What if all the darkness
surrounding them
turns him into a black dragon
or something?
[whimpers]
All the more reason
to beat this hydra fast
so we can get home, huh?
Oh, all right, fine!
If I've gotta do it,
I'm gonna do it.
[AQUA] But if Megumin's magic
doesn't work
I'm leaving you to deal
with this on your own!
[KAZUMA] Great, let's get
this show on the road!
♪
Hmm.
[MEGUMIN] Are we sure
she's purifying the lake?
It looks like
she's just swimming around.
[water splashing]
[KAZUMA] Apparently monsters
really don't like clean water.
Aqua purifies the lake
and when that makes
the hydra angry,
you make with the explosions.
- Hmph!
- Hey!
[DARKNESS]
I can't tell for sure,
but I think Aqua fell asleep
floating out into the middle
of the monster's lake.
[KAZUMA] Maybe we should've
tied something to her
so we could reel her in.
[gasps]
It's out there!
I can sense
incredible magical power!
Aqua, nap time's over!
[KAZUMA]
Wake up!
- [snoring]
- [KAZUMA] Aqua!
- [KAZUMA] Hey, Aqua!
- [yawning]
[DARKNESS]
Aqua, you have to wake up!
What's with all the racket?
- [yelling]
- Oh, wow.
The water's clean enough now
I can see right through it.
[AQUA] I guess that means
it's time for me to get out.
[gasps]
Kazuma, Kazuma, help!
There's something
gigantic down there
and I'm pretty sure
it's coming right for me!
[screams]
♪
[both whimpering]
Put me down!
I don't like it,
I wanna go home now, please!
- [AQUA] Somebody do something!
- [KAZUMA] Aqua!
This is bad!
I can't use Explosion magic
with her out there!
[MEGUMIN]
Aqua get out of there!
[Aldarp laughing]
♪
[AQUA]
Kazuma!
Kazuma, please!
I just wanna
go home to my baby!
[sobbing]
[screaming]
[KAZUMA]
Crap, this is really bad!
[AQUA] Take me home,
Take me home, Take me home,
Take me home!
[VERDIA]
Verdia here!
Did you say
the name Kazuma Satou?
I've heard about his antics
before once or twice.
Surprised to find out
he's still ali...